unilinc.edu.au 2015-05-01

# Privacy Policy | UNILINC

#### 1\. We respect your privacy

UNILINC Ltd respects a person's right to privacy and this policy sets out how we collect and manage your personal information.

"Personal information" is information we hold which is identifiable as being about you as a user of our systems and services.

#### 2\. The personal information we collect

In order for us to meet the library administrative requirements of our Member institutions, our Member institutions may supply the following types of personal information about you:

  * name
  * email address
  * postal address
  * phone number
  * fax number
  * course enrolment
  * patron status
  * patron ID
  * information about the systems and/or services you have with us as a Member or a client

In order to provide services directly to you we may collect the following types of personal information from you:

  * name
  * email address
  * postal address
  * phone number
  * fax number
  * information from enquiries you have made
  * communications between us
  * information about training courses you have done with us

#### 3\. How we collect your personal information

We collect personal information from you in a variety of ways including:

  * when a Member institution provides us with a file of data
  * when you interact with us electronically or in person
  * when you access our website
  * when we provide services to you.

#### 4\. Use of your personal information

We use your information to provide services to our Member institutions and through them to you or to you directly. We also use it to improve our services and to notify you of new systems and developments that we think you might be interested in or which UNILINC has contracted to implement.

We do not provide your information to third parties. We may provide your information to our systems vendor or other third parties who assist us in the provision of our systems and services to you. In every case we would seek permission from you. All such contracts or agreements identify that the entities will be bound by the same legislation as is applicable to UNILINC Ltd.

#### 5\. Security of your personal information

We have robust procedures to protect your personal information. However, we are not liable for any unauthorised access to this information. If any breach of private data is detected, we will take immediate steps to eliminate the breach and notify all those affected.

#### 6\. Access to your personal information

You can access and update your personal information by contacting us by phone or email as detailed below or by using any of the usual communication practices between UNILINC and its Members.

#### 7\. Complaints about privacy

If you have any complaints about our privacy practices, please feel free to send in details of your complaints to either the Executive Director or Associate Director using the contact details below. We take complaints very seriously and will respond shortly after receiving notice of your complaint. Please contact the UNILINC office via email: [info@unilinc.edu.au](mailto:info@unilinc.edu.au) or via telephone on +61 2 92831488.

#### 8\. Changes

Please be aware that we may change this Privacy Policy in the future. The revised versions will be uploaded onto our website. Please check occasionally.

#### 9\. Website

When you visit the UNILINC website

When you access our website we may collect certain information such as your browser type, operating system, the website you visited immediately before coming to our site, etc. This information is used in an aggregated manner to analyse how people use our site, so that we can improve our service.

Cookies

As is normal practice for companies, we use cookies on our website. Cookies are very small files which a website uses to identify you when you come back to the site and to store details about your use of the site. Cookies are not malicious programs that access or damage your computer. We use cookies to improve your experience of using our website.

Third party sites

Our site has links to other websites not owned or controlled by us. We are not responsible for these sites or the consequences of visiting those sites.

* * *

#### September 2013
